I just want to say this one last thing. The notion of saying Kamala Harris deserved a break
while the people of Gaza have continued to be broken repeatedly
and she is married to a Zionist and has said when she was on her campaign trail that she would
continue to support Israel in whatever they're doing is nonsensical to me. Like it's genuinely
mind-blowing to me that anyone would say Kamala Harris deserves a break. What about the migrants
whose countries have been destabilized by the United States sending them to the United States
to try to get money to send back to the people who couldn't come and were told do not come? What
about them? Did they get a break? Actually no! They didn't get a break. They got kidnapped. They're
getting kidnapped. So as much as I know that you deeply want to personalize this individual
you have to acknowledge the realities of their complicity when you try to disassociate them
from them. Like a couple minutes ago I was standing and I'm now sitting on my floor because I was brought
to my knees at seeing that the occupation forces have taken the life of an incredibly heroic journalist
Anas in Chesa and Yala talking about she deserves a break. None of us who care about actual people
have had a break. This is my cat Lumumba. Patrice Lumumba.